<resources>
<!--General-->
<string name="app_name">MultiplicationTableLearner</string>
<string name="greetings">Welcome to the Multiplication Table Learner!</string>
<string name="wanna_go_back">Do you really want to go back?</string>
<string name="confirm">Tap with one finger to confirm, to stay tap with multiple fingers</string>
<string name="provide_second_number">Provide second number </string>
<string name="get_result"> and get result by double swipe from right to left.</string>
<string name="times">times</string>
<string name="equals">equals</string>
<string name="congrats">Congratulations!</string>
<string name="unfortunately">Unfortunately no!</string>
<string name="ending_instruction">To start over, single swipe down.
        To repeat result, double swipe left. To quit, double swipe right.</string>
<!--Main Menu-->
<string name="main_menu">Main menu</string>
<string name="move_to_lm">To move to Learn Mode, swipe left with one finger.</string>
<string name="move_to_tm">To move to Test Mode, swipe left with two fingers.</string>
<string name="move_to_tt">To move to Tutorial, swipe left with three fingers.</string>
<string name="quit">To quit, swipe right with two fingers.</string>
<string name="want_to_quit">Do you really want to quit?</string>
<!--Learn Mode-->
<string name="learn_mode">Learn Mode</string>
<string name="provide_eq_or_num">Provide equation or a number</string>
<string name="is_result">is a result of</string>
<string name="multiplicand_is">Multiplicand is</string>
<!--Test Mode-->
<string name="test_mode">Test Mode</string>
<string name="is_correct">is correct!</string>
<string name="real_answer">The real answer is</string>
<!--Tutorial Mode-->
<string name="tutorial_mode">Tutorial Mode</string>
<string name="how_works">Here you can learn how the application works</string>
<string name="too_many_moves">Too many moves needed, try again</string>
    <string name="tut_instruction">To go through the whole tutorial, swipe down with one finger.
                            To go back, swipe right with two fingers.
                            To learn how to enter number, swipe left with one finger.
                            To learn how to provide equation, swipe left with two fingers.
                            To learn how Learn Mode works, swipe left with three fingers.
                            To learn how Test Mode works, swipe left with four fingers.</string>
    <string name="enter_digit_instruction">Numbers are entered digit by digit from left to right.
                            You enter a digit by tapping the screen.
                            The number of fingers you use is being added to the counter.
                            Digits are in the range of 0 to 9.
                            At the equivalent of ten, the counter resets.
                            Try to go through all the digits by tapping with a single finger 9 times.</string>
<string name="good_job">Good job!</string>
<string name="enter_digit2_instruction">Now try to enter digit 9 in just three moves by using multiple fingers</string>
    <string name="change_pos_instruction">To enter second digit, swipe left with one finger.
                            To erase last entered digit, swipe right with one finger.
                            Try to enter number 401.</string>
<string name="finished_enter_number">Now you know how to enter number!</string>
    <string name="provide_eq_instruction"> In order to provide second number, first you need to long press with one fingers.
                            That way you confirm entering the first one and move to the other.
                            Enter first number and hold one finger on the screen.</string>
    <string name="provide_sec_number">Now you can provide second number.
                            To confirm and get the result, swipe left with two fingers</string>
<string name="finished_provide_eq">Now you can provide the whole equation!</string>
<string name="lm_instruction_start">In Learn Mode you provide either a number or an equation</string>
    <string name="learn_mode_instruction">In both cases you confirm by swiping left with two fingers.
                            If you provide a number, you will hear all the possible equations that result in this number.
                            If you provide an equation, you will get the resulting number.
                            To hear the first provided number, swipe down with one finger</string>
<string name="finished_lm">Now you know how the Learn Mode works. Try it out!</string>
<string name="tm_instruction_start">In Test Mode you answer to the question asked by the program</string>
    <string name="test_mode_instruction">The question is either an equation to which you need to provide a result.
                            Or just a number, to which you should provide an equation.
                            In both cases you confirm by swiping left with two fingers.
                            To repeat question, swipe down with one finger.</string>
<string name="finished_tm">Now you know how the Test Mode works. Try it out!</string>
    <string name="finished_tutorial">You went through the whole tutorial!
                            If you still have problems, you can select proper chapter to repeat</string>
</resources>
